dlitall.com 2011-09-02

# Download the Latest Software, Games, DVD Movies, Music, TV Shows and ebooks! -

USERS ONLINE: ** 8395**   AVERAGE DOWNLOAD SPEED: **3942 KB/**s   TOTAL FILES: 3698415   NEW FILES: **1965**

## Privacy

Please make sure you have read the Privacy Policy before you subscribe to this website. It is your responsibility alone to be aware of this document and to read it. linewire.com - Download free and unlimited MP3s and movies! is committed to protecting your privacy. We provide this notice to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way information is collected and used. We will only use the information we collect for the purposes of providing you with a more personalized and useful membership experience. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. The Information We Collect: We only collect critical information in order to better serve our customers. A name, valid email address and password will be required of you for this. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on linewire.com - Download free and unlimited MP3s and movies! website. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name: Full name required for registration. Email address: To keep track of the different accounts. The Way We Use Information: We use this information to better supply the users with a customized service and support center, and to keep track of the different users' accounts. Our Commitment To Data Security: To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information: You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by emailing our technical support center (found in the Technical Support Area of the site). We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. How To Contact Us: Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please use our Technical Support link on the main site and fill in the form. We'll do our best to reply you as fast as possible. Notification: If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post notice of a privacy policy update on our Web site so that our members may view our updated policy on an ongoing basis and be aware of what information we collect.
